doublefine.com 2019-10-27

# Double Fine™ - What is Double Fine?

Double Fine values and respects its users' privacy, and we pledge always to treat our users fairly and to manage all data responsibly. 

On some parts of our website, such as our store and our forums, we may voluntarily collect payment information in order to fulfill merchandise orders you have placed, and require registration in order to participate in community discussion. 

Some of our games and some parts of our website may collect anonymous usage information to help improve your experience. If directly relevant to the game experience, and only with your explicit permission, some games may also access personal information for purposes you have specifically allowed. No information we collect will ever be sold to a third party or used for any purpose you have not authorized. 

More detailed information about our website and games is available below: 

## DOUBLE FINE GAMES

Some games developed by Double Fine may collect anonymous usage information in order to improve performance, game design, and other parts of the gameplay experience. Any usage statistics collected by our games will always be anonymized before they are sent back to Double Fine. They will never contain personally-sensitive information, and they will never be personally identifiable. 

Some games may, only when prompted by you, access personal information such as contacts, photographs, or music, to enhance the game experience. This will never occur without your explicit permission. Such functionality is purely opt-in. 

**What anonymous information is collected?**

Double Fine games may collect gameplay data, such as how long a user plays a given game in total or in a single session, how much of a game the player has completed, what equipment the player prefers, which in-app purchases are the most popular, and so on. They may also collect technical data such as hardware specifications, error logs, and crash data. 

**What do you do with that information?**

This information will be anonymized and aggregated for analysis, and used to improve the game experience. It will never be sold to a third party. It may, however, be shared in aggregated and summarized form for use only in educational materials or trade publications. No personal information will ever be used in this way. 

**What about games that access personal information?**

Some Double Fine games might, with your direct permission, access personal data such as contacts, photos, and music, only if directly relevant to the game experience. This information will never be accessed without your explicit request. If a game does not clearly ask for permission, it will never access any such information. This is a purely opt-in process. 

## THE DOUBLE FINE WEB SITE

When you browse our website, we collect no personally-identifying information. Anonymous usage information is collected only to gauge performance and make improvements to the website. Sections of our website that collect information are explained below. 

**_DOUBLE FINE STORE_**

Double Fine operates a merchandise store at the following address: [shop.doublefine.com](http://shop.doublefine.com/)

This store is hosted by Network Solutions, Inc. 

**What information is collected?**

When you purchase items from the store, you are required to provide your name, mailing address, email address, and payment information. 

**What do you do with that information?**

This information is collected information only so we can send you your goods and confirm your order. Payment processing is handled by Network Solutions, Inc. We will never share any of your information with a third party. 

**What about the mailing list?**

The Double Fine store includes a field to voluntarily submit your email address in order to subscribe to a mailing list. Signing up for this list is not required to purchase goods. If you sign up for the mailing list, your email address will only be used to send you occasional updates about Double Fine and its products. 

Your email address will never be provided to an unauthorized third party or used for any unauthorized purpose. Other than your email address, no personal information is associated with mailing list registration. 

**_DOUBLE FINE ACTION FORUMS_**

Double Fine hosts a discussion forum community at [doublefine.com/forums](http://www.doublefine.com/forums)

**What information is collected?**

In order to register for the Double Fine Action Forums, you must provide a valid email address. Forum registration does not require you to divulge your name or any personal information beyond your email address. 

**What do you do with that information?**

Your email address is only used to allow you to log in to your forum account and send you forum-related notifications in accordance with the forum account settings you specify. It will never be sold or provided to a third party, and it will never be used to send you marketing materials or other non-forum-related information you did not request. 

**_CHILDREN’S PRIVACY_**

The Double Fine website is not directed at children under the age of 13. To ensure users’ privacy, Double Fine Productions neither collects nor displays users’ age or date of birth anywhere on its website. 

## THE END

This information was last modified August 20, 2012. If you have any questions or concerns about Double Fine's privacy policy, website, or games, contact [support@doublefine.com](mailto:support@doublefine.com). Keep on keeping on. 

Mobile Version
